[
  {
    "question": "The html code executed by ________",
    "answer": "browser"
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML files are saved with which extension _______",
    "answer": ".html"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the closing tag in HTML _______",
    "answer": "</html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The root element of an HTML document is the ___________ tag.",
    "answer": "<html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The section that contains meta-information about the document ______",
    "answer": "<head>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the opening tag in HTML _______",
    "answer": "<html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Content that is visible on the web page is written inside the ___________.",
    "answer": "<body>"
  },
  {
    "id": "html_b_8",
    "question": "What is the tag used to represent the HTML version ____________",
    "answer": "<!DOCTYPE>"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the tag display the title of the web page ____________",
    "answer": "<title>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The collection of web pages __________",
    "answer": "website"
  },
    {
    "question": "Write the tag code display ratan bold text format __________",
    "answer": "<b>ratan</b>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code display ratan italic text format __________",
    "answer": "<i>ratan</i>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code display hyderabad underlined text format __________",
    "answer": "<u>hyderabad</u>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code display sleeping deleted text format __________",
    "answer": "<del>sleeping</del>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code formula of water can be written as H__________  O",
    "answer": "H<sub>2</sub>O"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code square of 5 can be written as 5__________",
    "answer": "5<sup>2</sup>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the tag code to mark highlight apple text is __________",
    "answer": "<mark>apple</mark>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag how to represent portion of text inside a paragraph ______",
    "answer": "<span>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag is used to display the largest heading in HTML _______",
    "answer": "<h1>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The tag used to display smaller text size is __________ ",
    "answer": "<small>"
  }
]
